Chapter-15.
Ethan Bruce POV
The penthouse was soundproof-a specification I'd insisted upon when I bought it.
Tonight, it proved to be a very good investment.
Leo Vance was no longer a Capo.
He was a heap of broken bones and bloody regret smeared across the designer rug.
I hadn't used a gun.
A gun was too quick.A gun was mercy.
Instead, I used my fists.
I used the heavy crystal ashtray.
I used the crushing weight of my boot heel.
Every time I heard a bone snap, I saw Aurora falling.
Snap.
That was for her broken arm.
That was for her bruised ribs.
Snap.
That was for the sheer terror she felt when the van door closed.
Leo had stopped moving ten minutes ago.
He was still breathing, but barely.
He would never walk again.
He would never hold a gun again.
I wiped my crimson-stained hands on his ruined silk shirt.
Then, I turned to Ilene.
She hadn't moved.She was huddled in the corner, her makeup running down her face in black streaks.
She looked like a weeping gargoyle.
"Ethan," she whimpered."I'm sorry.I'm sick.You know I'm sick.My father..."
"Don't," I said.
The mention of her father usually made me pause.
It usually made the guilt rise up and choke me.
But today?
Today, I felt nothing.
"Your father was a soldier," I said, my voice low as I stalked toward her.
"He died taking a bullet for me.
He died with honor."
I stopped in front of her.I towered over her.
"You have none."
"I love you!" she shrieked.
"I did it because I love you!"
"You don't love me," I spat.
"You love the power.You love the money.
You love that I was the only one who couldn't say no to you."
I reached down, tangling my fingers in her hair, and yanked.
She screamed.
I pulled her roughly to her feet.
"You are a traitor to this Family," I said.
"You conspired with a rival Capo to harm the wife of the Underboss."
"I'm a Ward!" she cried.
"You swore to protect me!"
"I swore to protect Ilene Wolf," I said.
"The daughter of a hero."
I dragged her toward the door.
"That woman is dead.
You killed her the moment you sold my wife to a monster."
She clawed at my hands.She kicked.She bit.
It didn't matter.
I was done being gentle.
I was done being the man who tried to balance the scales.
The scales were broken.
I dragged her into the elevator and pressed the button for the garage.
"Where are we going?" she sobbed.
"Ethan, please, don't kill me."
I looked at her reflection in the polished metal doors.
"Death is easy, Ilene," I said, my eyes locking with hers.
"You don't get off that easy."